collegehumor.com.au 2017-05-28

# Privacy Policy - CollegeHumor Australia

## PRIVACY POLICY

Thank you for visiting CollegeHumour.com.au (“Site”), a site operated by Turner International Australia Pty Ltd. and its affiliates ("Turner") pursuant to an agreement with Connected Ventures, LLC (“Connected Ventures”) (Turner and Connected Ventures collectively referred to herein as “we”, “our” or “us”). Your privacy is important to us. As such, we provide this privacy statement explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this general audience Turner site.

### THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

 _Personally Identifiable Information_

On occasion, you may enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities or otherwise participate in the Site’s activities and offerings. In the course of these various offerings, we often seek to collect from you various forms of personally identifiable information. Examples of the types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address and telephone number.

 _Non-Personally Identifiable Information_

We, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, and partners may collect various types of information that are anonymous, de-identified or otherwise not intended to personally identify you (“Non-Personally Identifiable Information”) when you visit our Site. A representative, non-exhaustive list of the types of Non-Personally Identifiable Information collected may include: network or Internet protocol address and type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Safari, Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Microsoft Windows or Mac OS), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g. Comcast, Verizon or AT&T), mobile network, device identifiers, advertising identifiers, sites visited before and after you visit the Site, the type of handheld or mobile device used to view the Site (e.g., iPhone, Blackberry), general location information (e.g. city, county, and/or state), the content and advertisements you have accessed, seen, forwarded and/or clicked on.

 _Geo-location Information_

If you are accessing the Site from a mobile device or through a mobile application, you may be asked to share your geo-location information with us so we can customize your experience on our Site. If you agree to such collection, you will be able to turn off such data collection at any time by accessing the privacy settings of your mobile device and/or through the settings in the applicable mobile application.

 _Information from Social Networks and Platforms_

You also can engage with our content, such as videos, applications, and other offerings, on or through third-party platforms and social networking sites, such as Facebook, or other third-party social media plug-ins and applications. When you engage with our content on or through third party social networking sites, plug-ins or applications, you may allow us to have access to certain personally identifiable information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information from your social media profile (e.g., name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, user files like photos and videos, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, the posts or the ‘likes’ you make, etc.) to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the Site. We may also obtain Non-Personally Identifiable Information (e.g., content viewed, game performance, high scores, and information about advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on through third-party platforms) from your interaction with our content.

Through some social networking sites’ privacy settings, you can control what information you share. For a description on how social networking sites handle your information, please refer to their privacy policies and terms of use.

### HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION

We may use the Information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you, to enforce the legal terms that govern your use of our Site, and/or for the purposes for which you provided the information.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter or notification, or to contact you about your account with us and for such other purposes as may be stated at the point where the information is collected.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, services or customized experiences.

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a letter to our editors, a posting to a discussion board or video), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us. We may on occasion combine information we collect through our Site with information that we collect from other sources. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, if you register and create a profile with our Site, the screen name you select as well as other content you submit to your profile (e.g., photos, comments, video, reviews) will be displayed publicly on the Site and may be reused and redistributed by us in our sole discretion, as set forth in our Terms of Use.

We, the Turner Affiliates, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our partners use the Non-Personally Identifiable information that is collected to improve the design and content of our Site, to deliver more relevant marketing messages and advertisements, to enable us to personalize your Internet experience, and to perform analytics. We also may use this information to analyze usage of our Site or content, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

When you provide information from your social media account, it can help enable us to do things like (1) give you exclusive content, (2) personalize your online experience with us within and outside our Site, (3) contact you through the social networking sites or directly by sending you the latest news, special offerings, and rewards, and (4) enable you to share your experience and content via social networking sites. By doing so, you consent to the use of this information in accordance with our privacy statement. When you provide personally identifiable information to us through an application, on our Site, or on social networking sites, it may be publicly viewed by other members of these sites and we cannot prevent further use of the information by third parties.

### INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

We may disclose information we have collected from you or the device used to access the Site in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or where we believe in our sole discretion it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Site and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements.

In addition, we may transfer information if we, or one of our business units, are acquired by, sold to, merged with or otherwise transferred to another entity.

Our agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this personally identifiable information in a manner that is consistent with this privacy statement and are not authorized to use the personally identifiable information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us.

We may disclose personally identifiable information and/or Non-Personally Identifiable Information to third parties whose practices are not covered by this privacy statement. For example, we may share such personally identifiable information we collect with our Turner Affiliates to provide, improve and communicate with you about their own products and services. 

We may also share such information with unaffiliated business partners and third parties (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you. If the Site shares personally identifiable information with such unaffiliated third parties, it will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses either at the point of submission of your personally identifiable information or prior to any such disclosure.

If you have signed up to receive our e-mails and prefer not to receive marketing information from this Site, follow the "unsubscribe" instructions provided on any marketing e-mail you receive from this Site. If you have signed up to receive text messages from us and no longer wish to receive such messages, you may follow the instructions to stop the delivery of such messages, which may include by replying “STOP” to the received text message.

This Site may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, promotions, games, applications, or social network integrations) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the Site activity. We have no control over these third parties' use of this information. The Site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such personally identifiable information.

To provide visitors with additional or more relevant product and service opportunities, to improve and personalize the Site and to perform analytics, and for the additional uses discussed in this privacy statement, we may share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with the Turner Affiliates, third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our partners.

### COOKIES, WEB BEACONS, ANALYTICS AND ADVERTISING

To enhance your online experience, we use "cookies" or similar technologies. Cookies are text files placed in your computer's browser to store your preferences.

We use cookies to understand Site and Internet usage and to improve or customize the content, offerings or advertisements on our Site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our Site. We also may use cookies to help us offer you products, programs, or services that may be of interest to you and to deliver relevant advertising.

We, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our partners also may use cookies to manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through the Site. This also helps us, our service providers and partners provide more relevant advertising.

The Adobe Flash Player is a powerful application and web tool that allows rapid development of highly dynamic content. This Site may employ locally stored objects (sometimes referred to as “Flash cookies”) in certain situations where we use Flash to provide special content such as video streaming, video on demand, video clips or animation. Flash (and similar applications) use this technology to remember settings, preferences and usage similar to browser cookies but Flash cookies are not managed through your web browser. You can access your Flash management tools from [Adobe’s websit](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html)e directly.

We, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies or our partners may also use "web beacons" or clear .gifs, or similar technologies, which are small pieces of code placed on a Site or in an email, to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a Site or email. For example, web beacons may be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that Site. Web beacons may also be used to provide information on the effectiveness of our email campaigns (e.g., open rates, clicks, forwards, etc.).

### HOW WE RESPOND TO DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS

At this time, this Site does not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, which may include “do not track” instructions. However, you can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser. You may set your browser to accept all cookies, block certain cookies, require your consent before a cookie is placed in your browser, or block all cookies. Blocking all cookies will affect your online experience and may prevent you from enjoying the full features offered at the Site. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information.

### ANALYTICS

We also use the services of reputable third parties to provide us with data collection, reporting, ad response measurement, and website and mobile application analytics, as well as to assist with delivery of relevant marketing messages and advertisements. These third parties may view, edit or set their own cookies. We, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies and/or partners may also place web beacons or similar technologies for these third parties. The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this privacy statement.

### AD CHOICES

Our goal at the Site is to provide you with ads that are relevant to you. Advertising enables us to provide the rich content for which Site is known. Often our ads are based on the content of pages you are viewing, but we also provide ads tailored to your interests. Our hope is that by presenting ads tailored to your interests, we will enhance your experience on the Site. As part of this process we, the Turner Affiliates, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our partners may collect information about your online activities on the Site and other sites, and supplement such information with information from third parties, in an effort to make inferences about your interests and deliver to you advertisements targeted to those interests.

For example, if you often visit content on another Turner site about travel, we may use “web beacons” to infer your possible interest in travel and may deliver an ad to you related to that interest. It's important to understand that these technologies use anonymous identifiers within the “cookies” stored in your browser. We offer you choices with regard to interest-based ads. To learn more about interest-based ads and the choices available to you, please visit our Ad Choices page.

### TURNER'S PARTICIPATION IN THE INDUSTRY SELF REGULATORY PROGRAM FOR INTEREST BASED ADS; ADDITIONAL CHOICE OPTIONS

Turner is a participant in the online industry’s self regulatory program administered by the Digital Advertising Alliance (the “DAA”) and has agreed to adhere to the DAA’s principles applicable to interest-based ads. Please visit the [Self Regulatory Program](http://www.aboutads.info/) for more information about the DAA, the self regulatory principles and choices you can make regarding interest-based ads.

You may also find more information about entities involved in online advertising and additional choices you may make through the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) at the [NAI site](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

The tools provided on the Ad Choices page, as well as the [DAA opt-out page](http://www.aboutads.info/) and the [NAI opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) are provided by third parties, not Turner. Turner does not control or operate these tools or the choices that advertisers and others provide through these tools.

### MOBILE DEVICE ADVERTISING AND TRACKING

We, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our partners may also be collecting identifiers designed to enable advertising on your mobile device. However, depending on your device, you may be able to reset your mobile device’s advertising identifier at any time by accessing the privacy settings on your mobile device. In addition, when using a mobile application you may receive tailored in-application advertisements. Each operating system, iOS for Apple phones, Android for Android devices and Windows for Microsoft devices, provides its own instructions on how to prevent the delivery of tailored in-application advertisements. You may review the support materials and/or the privacy settings for the respective operating systems in order to opt-out of tailored in-application advertisements. For any other devices and/or operating systems, please visit the privacy settings for the applicable device or contact the applicable platform operator.

### LINKED SITES

Our Site may contain links to or integrations with other sites such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, etc., whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

### INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER

Turner operates globally so it is necessary to transfer your information internationally. In particular, your information will likely be transferred to and processed in the United States where many of our central databases operate. The data protection and other laws of other countries, such as the United States, may not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using this Site you consent to your information being collected, used and transferred as set forth in this privacy statement.

### OUR COMMITMENT TO SECURITY

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data security, and to use correctly the information we collect online. These safeguards vary based on the sensitivity of the information that we collect and store.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this privacy statement.

### HOW YOU CAN ACCESS OR CORRECT INFORMATION

Access to personally identifiable information that is collected from our Site and that we maintain may be available to you. For example, if you created a password-protected account within our Site, you can access that account to review the information you provided.

You may also send an e-mail or letter to the following e-mail or street address requesting access to or correction of your personally identifiable information. For verification purposes please include your first name, last name, e-mail address and the password you use for such service.

Turner International Australia Pty Limited  
Attention: Privacy Officer  
Unit 804, 37 Bligh Street,  
Sydney NSW 2000  
Australia  
email:  [PrivacyAsiaPac@turner.com ](mailto:PrivacyAsiaPac@turner.com)  

### HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions or concerns about the online privacy statement for this site or its implementation you may contact us at [PrivacyAsiaPac@Turner.com](mailto:PrivacyAsiaPac@turner.com).

### UPDATES AND EFFECTIVE DATE

From time to time, we may update this privacy statement. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by sending an email message to the email address you most recently provided to us or by prominently posting a notice on our Site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this statement so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and with whom we share it.

The Privacy Statement posted on this Site was updated on 11 August, 2015.
